Hello everyone, today I’ll show you how to use the Medical Encyclopaedia by Javi and Álvaro,
Hola a todos, hoy les enseñaré a usar la Enciclopedia Médica de Javi y Álvaro,
a website for quickly and easily finding medical terms.
una página web para encontrar términos médicos de forma rápida y sencilla.
When you enter, you’ll see a search bar at the top and, just below, buttons with letters of the
Al entrar, verás una barra de búsqueda en la parte superior y, justo debajo, botones con letras del
alphabet. These allow you to easily navigate based on the initial letter of the condition you’re looking for.
abecedario. Estos te permiten navegar fácilmente según la inicial de la patología que buscas.
To find a condition, click on the letter that its name starts with, like “A”
Para encontrar una patología, haz clic en la letra por la que empieza su nombre, como “A”
for “allergies” or “anxiety” or “D” for “diabetes.” This will take you to an index
para “alergias” o “ansiedad” o “D” para “diabetes”. Esto te llevará a un índice
of conditions beginning with that letter. Within the index, select the specific condition
de patologías que comienzan con esa letra. Dentro del índice, selecciona la patología
you’re looking for. You’ll find a brief, direct explanation, and in some cases, charts or diagrams
específica. Encontrarás una explicación breve, directa y, en algunos casos, gráficos o diagramas
that help you understand the term quickly. You can return to the main menu or the
que ayudan a entender el término rápidamente. Puedes regresar al menú principal o a la
list of letters to continue exploring additional terms.
lista de letras para seguir explorando términos adicionales.
And that’s it! Now you know how to use the Medical Encyclopaedia by Javi and Álvaro
¡Y eso es todo! Ahora sabes cómo usar la Enciclopedia Médica de Javi y Álvaro
to consult medical terms quickly and effectively. Thanks for watching!
para consultar términos médicos de manera rápida y efectiva. ¡Gracias por mirar!